{"games": [{"questions": [{"content": ["Do more research to see if other sites say the same", "Believe it", "Ask a friend", "Change it to what you think is right"], "question": "You read something online that you are not sure is true or not. Do you:", "correct": 0}, {"content": ["Family members", "Birthdays", "Pet names", "All of the above"], "question": "You should not include ________ in a password:", "correct": 3}, {"content": ["Personal information can be used to harass or threaten you", "People will not read your page", "The best blogs are written anonymously", "Only famous people use their real names online"], "question": "Why should you NOT post personal information online?", "correct": 0}, {"content": ["Email address", "Home Address", "Phone number", "None of the above"], "question": "Which of the following information can you put on your social media profile?", "correct": 3}, {"content": ["You may say something that you do not mean when you are upset", "It is not easy for people to tell how you feel online", "You get in trouble with an adult", "All of the above"], "question": "Why should you never send emails, texts, or IMs when you are angry or upset?", "correct": 3}, {"content": ["Criticism", "Cyberbullying", "Nice", "Feedback"], "question": "Harassment through the internet that is rude and/or threatening is:", "correct": 1}, {"content": ["Nothing", "Scan it for viruses/malware", "Check the comments on the program page", "Do not install software from the internet"], "question": "What should you do before installing software from the internet?", "correct": 1}, {"content": ["Facebook", "Tik Tok", "Snapchat", "None of these"], "question": "Which of these social media sites are safe for kids?", "correct": 3}, {"content": ["Click okay, your parents and teachers will not mind", "Ask your parent or teacher permission to use the site", "Ask your friend for permission", "None of the above"], "question": "If a website asks for permission from a parent before you can use it, you should:", "correct": 1}, {"content": ["If you have been chatting with a friend online for several weeks and know that person well", "When your best friend has given out his/her information and nothing bad has happened", "If your online friend wants to meet you in a public place", "Never"], "question": "It is all right to give out personal information online in the following circumstances:", "correct": 3}, {"content": ["Give it to them if they give you their password", "Give it to your friend if they promise not to share it", "Tell your friend that you will not do it and explain why", "Give it to your friend but change your password after they are done"], "question": "Your friend wants to use your social media password to spy on someone that they can not see, but you can. Do you:", "correct": 2}, {"content": ["Something that is easy for you to remember, but hard for others to guess ", "Your birthday", "Something only you and your best friend know", "The name of your pet"], "question": "Your passwords should be:", "correct": 0}, {"content": ["See if you know anyone in common", "Accept them but limit what they can see", "Ignore/block the request", "Add them"], "question": "Someone tries to add you to their online network but you do not think you know who they are. Do you:", "correct": 2}, {"content": ["Not worry about it because it is only online", "Get parental permission", "Talk to a friend about what to do", "Both B and C"], "question": "Before putting personal information on a website I should:", "correct": 1}, {"content": ["Tell your parents and contact the site administrator.", "Create one of your own", "Show it to your friends", "Ignore it"], "question": "If someone creates a social-networking page (such as Facebook or Myspace) in your name, you should:", "correct": 0}]}]}